RG 005:034, Office of the Governor: John Dempsey (1961-1971)
Connecticut State Library
- Series 3. Subject Files, 1960-1971
  - Italy - Order of Merit Award to Gov. Dempsey, 1966 (Box A-266)
  - Jacobs Co. - Personnel Study Report (salary improvements, etc., for state employees), 1967 (Box A-266)
  - Jet Port, 1968-1970; 2 folders (Box A-266)
  - Jewett City Industrial Park, 1964 (Box A-266)
  - Johnson, Wilfred X. (re: Package Store Liquor Permit, 455 Barbour St., Hartford), 1963 (Box A-266)
  - Judges (complaints about not enough judges in the system), 1964 (Box A-266)
  - Judicial Districts, Committee to Study the Creation of, 1965 (Box A-266)
  - Judicial Systems of Other States, Commission to Study, 1963, 1965 (Box A-266)
  - Junk Yard (Joseph Francis) Southington (must read file for better description), 1961-1966 (Box A-266)
  - Juvenile Court Judges, 1967, 1969 (Box A-266)
  - Juvenile Court System, 1967, 1969 (Box A-266)
  - Juvenile Delinquency, 1961-1969 (Box A-267)
  - Juveniles, Interstate Compact on: Public Act 363, 1957 G.A., 1957-1970 (Box A-267)
  - Keep Conn. Clean and Beautiful, Citizens Committee to, 1967-1970; 6 inches (Box A-267)
  - Kennedy Memorial (Pres. John F. Kennedy), 1963-1967; 3 folders (Box A-268)
  - Kennedy, Robert F. (Attorney General as Vice President), 19,641,968 (Box A-268)
  - Kimberly Avenue Bridge (New Haven-West Haven), 1964-1965 (Box A-268)
  - Kindergarten Bill, 1967 (Box A-268)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr., 1968-1969 (Box A-268)
  - Kish (Rotzal) Case (murder case), 1960-1962 (Box A-268)
  - Labor Management Conference, 1962 (Box A-268)
  - Labor, U.S. Dept. of, 1961-1965 (Box A-268)
  - Lake Candlewood (boat ramp), 1968 (Box A-268)
  - Lake Waramaug (state park), 1968 (Box A-268)
  - Lake Waubeeka Association H.B. 6117, 1969 (Box A-268)
  - Land Acquisitions, 1968-1969 (Box A-268)
  - Land and Water Conservation Fund Act of 1963, S 859 -HR 3846, 1963-1965 (Box A-268)
  - Lane Bryant Annual Awards, 1965-1970 (Box A-269)
  - Lantern Hill, 1967 (Box A-269)
  - Latin American Countries - Exchange or Teachers, 1961-1962 (Box A-269)
  - Law Enforcement Assistance Act of 1965, 1966, 1968-1970 (Box A-269)
  - Law Enforcement Conference, 1965 (Box A-269)
  - Lead Paint Poison, 1969-1970 (Box A-269)
  - Legal Holidays, S.B. 920, 1969 (Box A-269)
  - Legislative Council, 1966-1967 (Box A-269)
  - Legislative Management Committee, 1969-1970 (Box A-269)
  - Liberty Bell, 1961, 1963-1964 (Box A-269)
  - Libraries, State Board of, Appointed December 5, 1963 (Library Improvement, Committee on), 1963-1965 (Box A-269)
  - Libraries, Governor's Commission on, 1961-1965, 1968-1969; 2 folders (Box A-269)
  - Library Committee, 1963 (Box A-269)
  - Library Improvement, Committee on, 1969 (Box A-269)
  - Library Services Study, 1967 (Box A-269)
  - Limited Repairers, HB 2542, 1962 G.A., 1963 (Box A-270)
  - Liquor, 1961-1962, 1964-1966, 1968 (Box A-270)
  - Liquor Bills, 1963-1965 (Box A-270)
  - Liquor Law Coordinating Committee (Sub. For HR 13, 1961 G.A.), 1962-1963 (Box A-270)
  - Liquor Permit Fees, 1961 (Box A-270)
  - Liquor Sales to Wholesalers, HB 4314 (Liquor Bills 1963 G.A.), 1967 (Box A-270)
  - Lobstering at Cerberus Shoal (Governor Rockefeller), 1960, 1962, 1966-1967 (Box A-270)
  - Lobstermen, 1961, 1965, 1967, 1969 (Box A-270)
  - Locate in Conn. - Industries Desiring to, 1962-1964, 1966, 1969 (Box A-270)
  - Long Island Sound Bridge, 1962-1969; 6 inches (Box A-270)
  - Lottery Tickets, 1961, 1965, 1967, 1969 (Box A-270)
  - Machiasport Oil Refinery, 1968-1969 (Box A-270)
  - Maintenance Programs for State Employees, Committee to Study, SA 490, 1959, G.A., 1959-1961 (Box A-270)
  - Manchester Community College, 1969 (Box A-271)
  - Manpower Development & Training Act of 1962, 1962-1965 (Box A-271)
  - Manwaring Property, SB 748, 1961, 1961-1970 (Box A-271)
  - Manufacturers Association of Conn., 1969 (Box A-271)
  - Marines, 1969-1970 (Box A-271)
  - Mass Merchandising Bill, 1969 (Box A-271)
  - Mass Transportation, Capitol Area, Conference on December 1, 1961 (Box A-271)
  - Mass. Income Tax Law, 1957-1960, 1964 (Box A-271)
  - Mayors' Conference, 1970 (Box A-271)
  - McCarthy, Eugene (Senator), 1968; 8 inches (Box A-271)
  - McCarthy, Eugene (Senator), 1968; 3 inches (Box A-272)
  - Meat Shipments, Rate on, 1961 (Box A-272)
  - Median Barriers, 1965-1967 (Box A-272)
  - Medical Care for the Aged, 1955, 1958-1961, 1963, 1969-1970 (Box A-272)
  - Medical-Dental School, 1961-1963, 1965; 3 folders (Box A-272)
  - Medical-Dental School, 1961-1962 (Box A-273)
  - Medical-Dental School, Commission to Select a Site, 1962-1963, 1969 (Box A-273)
  - Medical Services in Traffic Safety, 1961-1962 (Box A-273)
  - Meet the Press (Taping of Program on August 7, 1970) (Box A-273)
  - Memberships, Honorary Chairmanships, etc., 1961-1963, 1968-1970 (Box A-273)
  - Mental Health Center (New Haven), 1962-1964 (Box A-273)
  - Mental Health Councils, 1967-1968 (Box A-273)
  - Mental Health Dept. - Budget, 1961, 1963, 1965 (Box A-273)
  - Mental Health Planning, 1963-1965; 2 folders (Box A-273)
  - Mental Health Planning Project, Advisory Council, 1965 (Box A-273)
  - Mental Retardation Planning, State Committees on (Appointed by Gov. Dempsey, June 25, 1964), 1964-1967, 1969-1970 (Box A-274)
  - Mentally Retarded, 1961-1963, 1964-1967; 2 folders (Box A-274)
  - Mentally Retarded Children, Governor's Committee, 1956, 1956, 1964 (Box A-274)
  - Merritt Parkway Industrial Park, 1963, 1964 (Box A-274)
  - Metropolitan Regional Council (Tristate Transportation Agency), 1960-1961, 1964 (Box A-274)
  - Middletown, City of (Water Agreement, re: Conn. Valley Hospital and Board of Mental Health, 1963-1964, 1968 (Box A-274)
  - Migratory Labor, 1956, 1958-1960, 1965 (Box A-274)
  - Mildred Allen Memorial Fund, 1961-1963; 2 folders (Box A-274)
  - Milford Biological Laboratory, 1970 (Box A-275)
  - Milk, 1961-1970 (Box A-275)
  - Minimum Wage, 1955, 1957, 1961, 1967 (Box A-275)
  - Ministers Club, Gov. Dempsey's Speech, 1961 September 14 (Box A-275)
  - Minority Employment in State Service, 1970 (Box A-275)
  - Mississippi - Freedom Democratic Party, 1964 (Box A-275)
  - Mississippi Summer Project, 1964 (Box A-275)
  - Mitchell, David (refusing to register for the draft), 1967 (Box A-275)
  - Mobile Home Commission, S.A. 316, 1961 G.A., 1963-1965 (Box A-275)
  - Model Cities Program, 1967-1969, 1970; 2 folders (Box A-275)
  - Montville Water Works Company, 1966 (Box A-275)
  - Mortgage Authority, S.S.B. 813, 1969 (Box A-275)
  - Mosquito Control, 1962 (Box A-275)
  - Motor Boats, H.B. 5344, 1963, 1969 (Box A-275)
  - Motorcycle Helmets, H.B. 5785, 1969 (Box A-276)
  - Motorcycles, 1963 (Box A-276)
  - Mourning Doves, H.B. 3I657, P.A. 5A09, 1962-1963, 1967 (Box A-276)
  - Mourning Doves, Season on (out door space), 1968-1969 (Box A-276)
  - Mulliken Property, 1965 (Box A-276)
  - Municipal Employee Relations Act (Senate Bill 692), 1962 (Box A-276)
  - Mystic Marina, 1962 (Box A-276)
  - NAACP, 1961-1964, 1966-1967 (Box A-276)
  - Narcotics Advisory Council, P.A. 448, 1961 G.A., 1963, 1965-1967 (Box A-276)
  - NASA - National Aeronautics and Space Administration re: Proposed Electronic Research Facility Located in Conn., 1963-1964 (Box A-276)
  - National Convention - Gifts, 1968 (Box A-276)
  - National Guard, 1957-1962; 4 folders (Box A-276)
  - National Guard - Federal Troops, 1970 (Box A-276)
  - National Guard, Possible Reduction of - 43rd Division, 1962-1963 (Box A-276)
  - National Health Education Committee, 1961 (Box A-276)
  - Natural And Environmental Beauty, Governor's Conference on [1966] (Box A-276)
  - Naugatuck Footwear Plant of U.S. Rubber Co., re: Tariff on Imported Fabric Rubber-Soled Footwear, 1965-1966 (Box A-276)
  - Naugatuck Narcotics Problem, 1969 (Box A-277)
  - Naugatuck Valley Industrial Council, 1966 (Box A-277)
  - Naugatuck Valley Vocational Technical School, 1963-1964 (Box A-277)
  - Negroes in State Service, 1958, 1961, 1964, 1966-1967 (Box A-277)
  - New Britain Bill, S.H.B 8513, 1969 (Box A-277)
  - New Britain Charter, H.B. 5147, 1967 (Box A-277)
  - New Britain Memorial Hospital, 1958, 1961-1962 (Box A-277)
  - New Britain Route 72, 1961-1963 (Box A-277)
  - New Canaan Airport, 1963, 1965, 1969 (Box A-277)
  - New Canaan Armory, 1967 (Box A-277)
  - New Citizens (Letters to), 1963-1967; 2 folders (Box A-277)
  - New England Corrections Compact, 1964 (Box A-277)
  - New England Council, 1962, 1964, 1967-1968 (Box A-277)
  - New England Economic Development Region, 1964, 1966, 1969 (Box A-277)
  - New England Green Pastures Award, 1955-1956, 1958, 1962-1964 (Box A-277)
  - New England Interstate Water Pollution Control Commission, 1965-1966, 1968-1969 (Box A-278)
  - New England Regional Commission, 1968-1970; 11 inches (Box A-278)
  - New England Regional Commission, 1967-1969; 10 inches (Box A-279)
  - New England River Basin Commission, 1966-1969 (Box A-279)
  - New Haven Board of Education, 1965 (Box A-279)
  - New Haven County Home, 1954 (Box A-280)
  - New Haven - Interstate 91 (Mayor Lee), 1962 (Box A-280)
  - New Haven Real Estate Board, 1963-1964 (Box A-280)
  - New Haven Regional Center for Mentally Retarded, 1962, 1964 (Box A-280)
  - New Haven Riot (Photo, Inc.), 1967 (Box A-280)
  - New Haven - Route 34, 1965-1968 (Box A-280)
  - New Haven State Jail, 1960-1961, 1968 (Box A-280)
  - New London County Courthouse, 1967-1969 (Box A-280)
  - New London Hurricane Tidal Protection Project, 1963 (Box A-280)
  - New London Mentally Retarded Home, 1967 (Box A-280)
  - New York City Development Commission Reception, 1968 May 10 (Box A-280)
  - New York City Income Tax, 1966 (Box A-280)
  - New York City Income Tax, 1959, 1961-1962, 1966-1968 (Box A-280)
  - New York World's Fair, 1960-1966; 12 inches (Box A-281)
  - New York World's Fair, 1960-1966; 7 inches (Box A-282)
  - New York World's Fair - Conn. Advisory Commission, 1962-1964; 2 folders (Box A-282)
  - Newington Home and Hospital Deed, re: Mental Retardation Center, 1964 (Box A-282)
  - Newspaper Editors, 1965-1967 (Box A-282)
  - Newtown - I-84, 1970 (Box A-282)
  - Niantic Bay and Harbor, 1961, 1964, 1965 (Box A-282)
  - North Branford Elderly Housing, 1969 (Box A-282)
  - Northeastern Conn. Regional Community College, 1967 (Box A-282)
  - Northeastern Regional Transportation Committee, 1967 (Box A-282)
  - Northeastern Resources Commission, 1962, 1967 (Box A-282)
  - Northeastern Resources Commission, 1957-1958, 1960-1962, 1967 (Box A-282)
  - Northford-Wallingford, re: Toll-free Telephone Service, 1961 (Box A-283)
  - Northwestern Conn. Community College, 1965-1967, 1969; 2 folders (Box A-283)
  - Norwalk Armory, 1968 (Box A-283)
  - Norwalk Community College, 1965-1967 (Box A-283)
  - Norwich Fire - Van Tassel Leather Co., 1962 (Box A-283)
  - Norwich Flood, 1963 (Box A-283)
  - Norwich Free Academy, 1963 (Box A-283)
  - Notices to Subdivision of the State P.A. 406 Vetoed, 1961 (Box A-283)
  - Nuclear Research Center, 1961-1963; 4 folders (Box A-283)
  - Nystrom's Pond Dam, 1962-1969 (Box A-283)
  - "Objectionable Magazines and Literature" and Films, 1958-1959, 1963-1964, 1967 (Box A-284)
  - Obscenity and Pornography Commission, 1967, 1969-1970 (Box A-284)
  - Oceanographic Foundation, 1966-1967, 1969 (Box A-284)
  - Oceanography, 1969 (Box A-284)
  - Oil Imports, 1969-1970 (Box A-284)
  - Oil Pollution, 1969 (Box A-284)
  - Oil Shortage, 1970 (Box A-284)
  - Old Saybrook - North Cove Project, 1964 (Box A-284)
  - Open Spaces Program (William H. Whyte Report), 1961-1963, 1968 (Box A-284)
  - Operation Breakthrough, 1967-1968 (Box A-284)
  - Operation Sail, 1967-1968 (Box A-284)
  - Opticians, 1965 (Box A-284)
  - Optometry, 1961, 1968 (Box A-284)
  - "Organization and Functions of Conn. State Government", 1960, 1964; 2 folders (Box A-284)
  - Orthodox Church, 1965 (Box A-284)
  - O'Sullivan, Matthew, Appointment as Director of Collection and Accounting, 1959-1960 (Box A-284)
  - Our Lady of Fatima School - Wilton, Conn., 1964 (Box A-284)
  - Outdoor Recreation, 1962-1963, 1967 (Box A-284)
  - Outdoor Recreation Plan, 1965; 2 folders (Box A-284)
  - Oxford Airport, 1963, 1965-1970 (Box A-285)
  - Oxoboxo River, Montville, Conn., 1962-1963 (Box A-285)
  - Pardons, Board of, 1955-1960, 1963, 1967-1968; 3 folders (Box A-285)
  - Park River - Hartford, 1969 (Box A-285)
  - Park River Water Shed, North Branch, Hartford County, Hartford, 1959, 1961 (Box A-285)
  - Parking (Hartford Post Office & Vicinity), 1966-1968 (Box A-285)
  - Parking Lease, Brewery St. Postal Station, New Haven, 1966 (Box A-285)
  - Parole, Board of, 1957, 1962, 1967-1970 (Box A-285)
  - Partners of the Alliance (Conn. and Paraiba, Brazil), 1964-1967, 1969; 2 folders (Box A-285)
  - Partners of the Alliance (Conn. and Paraiba, Brazil), 1967-1970 (Box A-286)
  - Party Enrollments, 1968 (Box A-286)
  - Party Level, 1963 (Box A-286)
  - Passamaquoddy Tidal Power Project, 1964-1965 (Box A-286)
  - Pediatric Cardiac Care, 1963 (Box A-286)
  - Penn Central Co., 1969 (Box A-286)
  - "Penny Bill" - An Act Defining Bottle Price for the Purpose of the Liquor Control Act, 1961 (Box A-286)
  - People-to-People, 1962-1963, 1965 (Box A-286)
  - Pesticides, 1964; 2 folders (Box A-286)
  - Peters, James S. II, 1962 (Box A-286)
  - Phoenix Mutual Life Insurance Co., 1965 (Box A-286)
  - Picketing of Governor's Residence, 1965 (Box A-286)
  - Pine Acres, 1963 (Box A-286)
  - Plainville Ramps, 1966 (Box A-286)
  - Planning & Zoning, 1967 (Box A-286)
  - Plans for Progress, 1969 (Box A-286)
  - Police Review Boards, 1965 (Box A-286)
  - Police Training Committee, Governor's Municipal, 1958-1960, 1962, 1964-1965 (Box A-287)
  - Polio Vaccine, 1961-1962 (Box A-287)
  - Polish - Appointees, undated (Box A-287)
  - Poll Tax, 1963 (Box A-287)
  - Port Authority, 1967-1968 (Box A-287)
  - Portrait, 1958-1959, 1970 (Box A-287)
  - Postmaster - Woodstock, 1963 (Box A-287)
  - Poverty Bill (Economic Opportunity Act of 1964), 1964-1968; 3 folders (Box A-287)
  - Power Lines Across the Connecticut, 1966 (Box A-287)
  - Praise, Appreciation, etc. (Letters), 1961-1968 (Box A-287)
  - Prayers in Public Schools, 1962-1964, 1967, 1969 (Box A-287)
  - Predicting Highway Fatalities in Advance of a Holiday, 1961 (Box A-287)
  - Presidential Elections, 1964, 1968 (Box A-287)
  - Priests (re: Ordination), 1962 (Box A-287)
  - Probate Court Records, 1969 (Box A-287)
  - Probate Courts, 1969 (Box A-288)
  - Project Equality, 1965-1967, 1969 (Box A-288)
  - Property Tax, 1962-1963, 1965-1970; 2 folders (Box A-288)
  - Psychiatric Aides and Clinics, 1961, 1967 (Box A-288)
  - Psychiatric Clinics for Children, 1969 (Box A-288)
  - Public Act 34, 1963 (Box A-288)
  - Public Investment Planning, 1970 (Box A-288)
  - Public Roads in the State, Committee to Reclassify All, 1960 (Box A-288)
  - Public Transportation Assistance Act of 1969 (Box A-288)
  - Puerto Ricans, 1969 (Box A-288)
  - Race Tracks, 1963 (Box A-288)
  - Radiation Workers, Compensation Act, 1962 (Box A-288)
  - Real Estate Bills, 1961 (Box A-288)
  - Real Estate Brokers, 1965 (Box A-288)
  - Reapportionment, 1962-1965; 4 folders (Box A-288)
  - Recall, 1965, 1967, 1969 (Box A-289)
  - Recipes, 1965, 1967 (Box A-289)
  - Records Management Committee, 1957 (Box A-289)
  - Recreation, Governor's Conference on, September 12, 1960 (Box A-289)
  - Red Cross, 1955-1960, 1962-1964 (Box A-289)
  - Reeves Soundcraft Corp., 1962-1963 (Box A-289)
  - Refuse Disposal, 1969 (Box A-289)
  - Regional Community Colleges [out to Governor's office] (Box A-289)
  - Regional Plan Association [1956, 1966-1969] (Box A-289)
  - Regional Planning, 1959, 1961-1962; 2 folders (Box A-289)
  - Registered Nurses, 1970 (Box A-289)
  - Registration and Voting Participation, 1964 (Box A-289)
  - Reid, Benjamin, 1959-1963 (Box A-289)
  - Religious Traffic Safety Weekend, 1956-1961 (Box A-289)
  - Removal of Illegally Parked Out-of-state Motor Vehicles Plates, 1968 (Box A-290)
  - Rent Control, 1958-1959, 1968 (Box A-290)
  - Republican Party Rules, 1967 (Box A-290)
  - Research Advisory Committee, 1961-1965, 1967-1970; 2 folders (Box A-290)
  - Research Center, 1965, 1968 (Box A-290)
  - Research Commission, 1965-1967; 2 folders (Box A-290)
  - Retarded Children, 1961, 1963-1965, 1969-1970 (Box A-290)
  - Retired Teachers, 1962-1963 (Box A-291)
  - Retraining of Industrial Workers (Pilot Program), 1961-1963 (Box A-291)
  - Revitalize Urbia Days, 1970 March 13-15 (Box A-291)
  - Reward, 1956-1957, 1962, 1964, 1966-1967, 1970 (Box A-291)
  - Ribicoff, Abraham - Background Material (Box A-291)
  - Right to Work, 1965, 1967-1969 (Box A-291)
  - Riot Procedure, 1967 (Box A-291)
  - Rivers and Harbors Congress, 1962-1965, 1967 (Box A-291)
  - Rochambeau Commission - Interstate Commission, 1953-1955 (Box A-291)
  - Rock Festival - Powder Ridge, 1970 (Box A-291)
  - Rocky Hill Correctional Center, 1969 (Box A-291)
  - Rocky Neck State Park re: Pipeline Easement, 1964 (Box A-291)
  - Ross Pond (Norman), 1963 (Box A-291)
  - Ross Realty Co., 1969 (Box A-291)
  - Route 6, 1964-1966 (Box A-291)
  - Route 7, 1961-1963, 1965; 2 folders (Box A-291)
  - Route 7, 1967-1968 (Box A-292)
  - Route 8, 1958-1966, 1968-1969; 3 folders (Box A-292)
  - Route 9, 1963-1966 (Box A-292)
  - Route 25, 1964-1965 (Box A-292)
  - Route 39 - re: Danbury - New Fairfield, 1976 (Box A-292)
  - Rural and Urban Development Committee, 1966 (Box A-292)
  - Sacred Heart Academy, 1965 (Box A-292)
  - Safety Pins, re: Tariffs on, 1965 (Box A-292)
  - St. Francis Hospital (Committee of 1,000), 1967-1968 (Box A-292)
  - St. Joseph Catholic School, 1970 (Box A-292)
  - Sales Tax, 1961, 1963, 1965, 1967, 1968 (Box A-293)
  - Salmon River, 1968 (Box A-293)
  - Sanders, William J., Commissioner of Education, 1966 (Box A-293)
  - Sarner, Sydney (Estate of), 1970 (Box A-293)
  - Saunders, Robert (Alias Robert Lee Sanders), 1955-1957, 1961-1964 (Box A-293)
  - Savarin Restaurants, 1961-1964 (Box A-293)
  - Savings Banks re: Demand Deposits, 1969 (Box A-293)
  - Savings Banks Life Insurance, 1967-1969 (Box A-293)
  - Savings Bonds, 1969 (Box A-293)
  - Schacht, Herbert T., 1962, 1965-1966, 1970 (Box A-293)
  - School Bus Safety, 1966, 1969 (Box A-293)
  - School Bus Transportation Bill, 1961 (Box A-293)
  - School Children [also includes undated homemade book], 1958-1959, 1961-1968, 1970 (Box A-293)
  - School Lunch, 1967 (Box A-293)
  - School Lunch Program, 1967 (Box A-293)
  - Schwarzenback Memorial Fund, 1962-1963 (Box A-293)
  - Science Fair, 1966-1967 (Box A-293)
  - Scofield Dump (Stamford), 1969 (Box A-293)
  - Screening Committee [1955-1957, 1964, 1970] (Box A-294)
  - Seattle World's Fair [1962] (Box A-294)
  - Security Treatment Center [1963-1966, 1969-1970] (Box A-294)
  - Selective Service (Box A-294)
    - Act of 1967, 1966-1967; 2 folders (Box A-294)
    - Appointments - Recommendations, 1957-1958, 1961-1965 (Box A-294)
    - Calls, 1955-1958, 1961-1965 (Box A-294)
    - Certificates of Appreciation, 1955-1965 (Box A-294)
    - General, 1963-1964, 1966-1967 (Box A-294)
    - Resignations, 1958-1959, 1961-1962, 1963-1965 (Box A-294)
    - System, 1966-1969; 2 folders (Box A-294)
    - Vacancies, 1958, 1965, 1962 (Box A-294)
  - Senate Transcript, 1969 June 4 (Box A-295)
  - Senator, U.S., re: Certification of Election as, 1964, 1968, 1970 (Box A-295)
  - Senior Citizens Health Insurance, 1961 (Box A-295)
  - Servoss, Robert M., re: Jesse Doyle (State Ward), 1961-1962 (Box A-295)
  - Shakespeare Festival Theater and Academy - Stratford, Conn., 1962, 1964-1965 (Box A-295)
  - Shennecossett Golf Course, 1967-1968 (Box A-295)
  - Sheriffs (Deputies), re: Highway Patrol Duty, 1962 (Box A-295)
  - Shore Line Areas, 1961-1962 (Box A-295)
  - Signs - Road Construction, 1962 (Box A-295)
  - Silver Lane - East Hartford, 1970 (Box A-295)
  - Silver Sands State Park, 1963, 1968 (Box A-295)
  - Silverware Industry, re: Tariffs, 1964 (Box A-295)
  - Sisters of the Immaculate Conception (Matulaitis Nursing Home, Putnam), 1964 (Box A-295)
  - Skill Center, 1966-1967 (Box A-295)
  - Slaughter (Humane), 1961, 1966 (Box A-295)
  - Small Business Administration, 1961 (Box A-295)
  - Smith, Cyril K. - Social Security System, Municipalities Participating in, 1958-1961 (Box A-295)
  - Song Program, New Britain, 1956-1959, 1968-1970 (Box A-295)
  - South Central Community College, 1967 (Box A-295)
  - Southeastern Conn. Water Authority, 1969 (Box A-295)
  - Southern New England Telephone Company - Rate Increase, 1963, 1965, 1969 (Box A-295)
  - Southington Board of Education, re: Bus Service for School Children, 1961, 1962, 1966, 1968 (Box A-295)
  - Special Education, 1967-1968 (Box A-296)
  - Special Education - Children, 1965-1966 (Box A-296)
  - Special Session, 1963-1965, 1969-1970; 11 folders (Box A-296)
  - Special Session, re: Unemployment, 1970 (Box A-296)
  - Speeding Arrests and No Exceptions, 1965 (Box A-296)
  - Stamford Bills HB 8597 and 7091, 1969 (Box A-296)
  - Stamford Branch (UCONN), 1962 (Box A-296)
  - Stamford Branch (UCONN) Building: Elevator, 1962 (Box A-296)
  - Stamford Day Care Center (Mental Health Department), 1961-1962 (Box A-296)
  - Stamford Traffic Light (Bull's Road), 1961 (Box A-296)
  - State Agency Periodicals, 1961 (Box A-296)
  - State Agency Regulation, 1963 (Box A-296)
  - State Building Program Commission, 1957-1959, 1963, 1965, 1969 (Box A-296)
  - State Cars, 1959-1960, 1962, 1964, 1966-1970 (Box A-296)
  - State Capitol and Bushnell Park Area, City-State Liaison Committee, 1964, 1966-1967 (Box A-296)
  - State Colleges (Budget), 1961, 1967-1968 (Box A-296)
  - State Employees, 1964-1970; 5 folders (Box A-297)
  - State Employees - Appeals, 1963 (Box A-297)
  - State Employees Association, 1961-1966; 3 folders (Box A-297)
  - State Employees Association, 1962, 1965; 2 folders (Box A-298)
  - State Employees - Overtime Payment, 1963 (Box A-298)
  - State Employees Retirement System, 1970 (Box A-298)
  - State Government Organization Report, February 1950, 1950, 1970 (Box A-298)
  - State Home Ownership Program (1-1/2%), 1956-1957 (Box A-298)
  - State Income Tax, 1961, 1963, 1965-1970; 2 folders (Box A-298)
  - State Labor Relations, 1962-1963 (Box A-298)
  - State Planning Council, 1967-1969 (Box A-298)
  - State Scholarship Commission, 1963-1970; 2 folders (Box A-298)
  - State Song Contest: (Sponsored by Women's Auxiliary of Home Builders Association of Hartford County), 1962-1968, 1970 (Box A-298)
  - State Technical Colleges, 1968 (Box A-298)
  - State Technical Services Act of 1965, 1965-1967 (Box A-298)
  - Stepfathers: Welfare Dept. Policy, 1963-1964 (Box A-299)
  - Stock Exchange, 1966-1967 (Box A-299)
  - Stock Exchange - Conn. Development Commission Report to, 1962 (Box A-299)
  - Straight Pins - Increase in Tariff, 1964 (Box A-299)
  - Stratford Board of Education, 1967 (Box A-299)
  - Student Loan Foundation, Conn., 1967 (Box A-299)
  - Student Newspapers - Editor-in-Chief Invitations, 1962 April 14 (Box A-299)
  - Student Voting (Letters to Public and Private Colleges in Conn.), 1962, 1964, 1966 (Box A-299)
  - Stutz, Robert L. (Review of Grievance Procedure of Classified State Employees), 1960-1961 (Box A-299)
  - Summer Employment, 1968 (Box A-299)
  - Sunday Drinking Hours, 1963 (Box A-299)
  - Sunday Liquor Hours, 1969 (Box A-299)
  - Superintendent of Schools, 1970 (Box A-299)
  - Surplus Foods, 1959, 1967-1969 (Box A-299)
  - Surplus Property and Food, 1959, 1965-1967 (Box A-299)
  - Talcott Mountain (Times Tower), 1965-1967 (Box A-299)
  - Tarawa, 1951, 1953, 1957 (Box A-299)
  - Tarawa, 1955, 1969 (Box A-300)
  - Task Force on Education, 1969 (Box A-300)
  - Tax on Municipal Utilities, 1963 (Box A-300)
  - Tax Program, 1969 (Box A-300)
  - Tax Study - State of Conn., by Alfred G. Buehler, 1963 (Box A-300)
  - Taxes, 1961-1964, 1967-1969 (Box A-300)